<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SL4GCompose</string>

    <!-- Navigation Strings -->
    <string name="home_tab">Home</string>
    <string name="artist_tab">Artists</string>
    <string name="quiz_tab">Quiz</string>
    <string name="media_tab">Media</string>
    <string name="contact_tab">Contact</string>

    <!-- Group Info -->
    <string name="sl4g_logo">SL4G_Logo</string>
    <string name="sl4g_name">SwitchinLanes</string>
    <string name="sl4g_name_full">SwitchinLanes4God</string>
    <string name="sl4g_photo_description">SwitchinLanes Image Logo</string>
    <string name="sl4g_bio">"SwitchinLanes" (SL4G) was founded in 2014 by Deane Walden.
        The group consists of 6 members: Ronald Easley (Ron Rhythm), Michael Ebron (Ookie Ebron),
        Samuel McFadden Jr. (S.H.E.E.S.H.), Justin Shelton (JuJu), and Jerimy Mask (JMask).
        The majority currently reside on the outskirts of Richmond, Virginia.
        Each member of the group has profound life changing testimonies that ultimately drew them
        together, and it all begins with Founder, Deane Walden.
        -SwitchinLanes-
    </string>

    <!-- Artists Info -->
    <string name="deane_full_name">Deane Walden</string>
    <string name="deane_bio">Deane Walden was born and raised in Richmond, VA.
        Prior to the formation of SwitchinLanes, Deane focused on the production of secular music
        with another group by the name of “Paperchasers”. After nine consecutive years of promoting
        sex, drugs, and violence, conviction finally struck like a jolt of lightning causing Deane
        to surrender his life to Christ. He immediately turned his life around and initially
        believed that giving up music was a part of the process until God told him otherwise.
        Shortly after, Deane was inspired to create the group “SwitchinLanes4God” signifying not
        only his change, but his commitment to The Most High. The pursuit for members had begun.
    </string>

    <string name="ron_full_name">Ron Rhythm</string>
    <string name="ron_bio">Ron Rhythm was born in Germany, but later moved to the United States
        where he settled in Richmond, VA. He lived a pretty peculiar lifestyle as a street drag
        racing secular R &amp; B artist. He first met founder, Deane Walden before he was saved, however
        after he Switched Lanes he began attending church growing a closer bond with God and the
        newly founded group.
    </string>

    <string name="ookie_full_name">Ookie Ebron</string>
    <string name="ookie_nick_name">"Dread"</string>
    <string name="ookie_bio">Ookie Ebron was born in Albany, New York but moved to Richmond Virginia
        at the age of seven. He was raised in the Christian faith but didn\'t develop a relationship
        with Jesus Christ until the age of seventeen. He began to struggle with his desire to chase
        women, always searching for companionship to cover the void of love that eluded his life
        where only Christ could fill. Ookie experienced a life changing encounter with The Holy
        Spirit at Winterfest 2010 in Gatlinburg Tennessee. Since that experience, Ookie has begun to
        bear his cross and venture into different aspects of ministry. He has served in children\'s
        ministry, street evangelism, and even spoken in the pulpit before God revealed to him, the
        gift of music. Ookie takes great delight in serving and is looking forward to more
        opportunities to spread the Gospel!
    </string>

    <string name="sam_full_name">Samuel McFadden</string>
    <string name="sam_nick_name">"S.H.E.E.S.H."</string>
    <string name="sam_bio">S.H.E.E.S.H. was born and raised in Richmond, VA. He was groomed heavily
        in the Christian faith but turned away and rebelled every chance he got. This sent
        S.H.E.E.S.H. spiraling down a pathway of self-destruction. After being incarcerated twice,
        God softened his heart and S.H.E.E.S.H. finally opened his heart to Jesus. From that point
        forward he began attending a local ministry as a result of an invitation from group member,
        JMask, where he would later introduce others. Henceforth S.H.E.E.S.H. has remained a soldier
        in the army of the Lord using music as his weapon.
    </string>

    <string name="juju_full_name">Justin Shelton</string>
    <string name="juju_nick_name">"JuJu"</string>
    <string name="juju_bio">JuJu was born in Richmond, VA. He was raised in the Christian faith at
        a young age, but turned away from his faith choosing to live a street lifestyle. At the age
        eighteen he rededicated his life to Christ, but due to the lack of spiritual nourishment, he
        turned away from his faith a second time. Two years later he experienced a near death
        altercation leaving him with thirteen stab wounds causing him to lose his right eye
        completely. During his healing process, he was invited to a local ministry by group member
        S.H.E.E.S.H. where he decided to truly commit to Christ with the desire to tell everyone
        about His amazing grace.
    </string>

    <string name="jmask_full_name">Jerimy Mask</string>
    <string name="jmask_nick_name">"JMask"</string>
    <string name="jmask_bio">JMask is a student-athlete born and raised in Richmond, VA, but like
        many others, the street life appealed more to him. As a result of a school expulsion in the
        11th grade, he connected with a pastor’s daughter. With the intentions of spending time with
        this young lady, JMask attended church services, prayer services, and bible studies where
        God began to open his heart. A year later he became a new creation in Christ. JMask believes
        that because he was never introduced to the Gospel growing up that it is his duty to tell
        the world about his Jesus, whether it’s through the music of SwitchinLanes or evangelism,
        Jesus will be proclaimed.
    </string>

    <!-- Album Names -->
    <string name="album_a_road_less_traveled">A Road Less Traveled</string>
    <string name="album_water_walking">Water Walking</string>
    <string name="album_no_longer_bound">No Longer Bound</string>
    <string name="album_rhythm_of_heaven">Rhythm Of Heaven</string>
    <string name="album_no_brakes">No Brakes</string>

    <!-- URLS -->
    <string name="sl4g_website_url">"http://www.sl4g.com"</string>
    <string name="sl4g_email">"switchinlanes4god@gmail.com"</string>

    <!-- Album URLS -->
    <!-- A road less traveled, Water walking,  as well as No Longer Bound were listed as mixtapes and not available for purchase.
     These were hosted on the SL4G site. Will find somewhere to host and update. -->
    <string name="album_a_road_less_traveled_url">"https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1s-JivBs-qW3yF0OeLCBH-FBRXWxTmlVw?usp=drive_link"</string>
    <string name="album_water_walking_url">"https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/10Naearpw4F3rMYDnX1Rk0GtmDUKNibjx?usp=drive_link"</string>
    <string name="album_no_longer_bound_url">"https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1XHTHIiq2O9zAjSHCun1UnRwzgILFzY7f?usp=drive_link"</string>
    <string name="album_rhythm_of_heaven_url">"https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/rhythm-of-heaven/1216497679"</string>
    <string name="album_no_brakes_url">"https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/no-brakes/1343983901"</string>

    <!-- Social Media URLS -->
    <string name="instagram_url">"http://www.instagram.com/switchinlanes4g"</string>
    <string name="twitter_url">"http://www.twitter.com/switchinlanes4g"</string>
    <string name="youtube_url">"http://www.youtube.com/user/switchinlanes4god"</string>


    <!-- App Assets -->
    <string name="referenceYoutubeTag">Please visit the Youtube link above to access more of our videos!</string>
    <string name="music_videos_tag">Music Videos</string>
    <string name="discography_tag">Discography</string>
    <string name="discography_sub_tag">(Swipe Album below to cycle projects)</string>
    <string name="contactPrompt">We greatly appreciate you all taking part on this journey with us as we walk closer to Christ. Please take the opportunity to reach out to us. Rather it be for prayer or to book The Lanes!</string>
    <string name="name_heading">Name:</string>
    <string name="name_enter_hint">Enter Name</string>
    <string name="phone_number_heading">Phone Number:</string>
    <string name="text_heading">Text:</string>
    <string name="message_heading">Message:</string>
    <string name="text_enter_hint">How can we serve you?</string>
    <string name="submit_button_label">Submit</string>
    <string name="book_us_button_label">Book Us</string>
    <string name="show_less">Show less</string>
    <string name="show_more">Show more</string>
    <string name="cannot_send_email_message">Unable to send email, please check input</string>



</resources>